### Contact

evelyn.paplauskas@outlook.c

www.linkedin.com/in/evelyn-paplauskas-13a012186 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

**Customer Service** 

Sales

Telemarketing

### Certifications

How to Slow Down and Be More Productive

# **Evelyn Paplauskas**

--

Kingswood, New South Wales, Australia

## Summary

Nearly two decades of customer service in both telephone and retail sales. Familiar with brand execution at a front line level. Experience includes using CRM systems such as SAP ERP/CRM and BASIS as well as POS systems.

Hobbies include anything remotely related to computer programming, web/app development and linux systems. I also enjoy live theatre, musicals, stage productions, science fiction novels and shows.

## Experience

All About You Care and Supports Administrative Assistant and In-house Software Solution Creator January 2020 - Present (3 months)

Gateshead, NSW

Assist with administrative tasks using both Xero and Deputy, MS Office and additional software

- -Self directed time management whilst working remotely from home
- -Regular attendance in office for training and business development discussions
- -Documentation of business processes and proposing improvements
- -Leveraging previously self learned knowledge of web development and IT solutions to build in-house tools for greater efficiency
- -Concurrently studying in a "Fast Track" Front-End Developer Bootcamp at Coder Academy with a view of improving tools utilised by All About You Care and Supports

Hilti Australia Customer Service Specialist April 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 9 months) Sydney, Australia

-Diverse communication delivery and response by phone, email and webchat to meet needs of customers whilst providing in-house sales support for retail store persons and field sales agents.

- -Being aware of full product portfolio including the tool or consumable product usage and their relevant specifications
- -Determine appropriate solution for customer by active listening to ensure best outcome in sales and support
- -Tracking and resolving issues with deliveries and customer expectations

Coca-Cola Amatil
Customer Service Representative
January 2010 - March 2017 (7 years 3 months)
Sydney, Australia

Sales and service via telephone, email and fax correspondence.

The majority of the time in this position I was assigned a regular telephone sales route. This involved managing my time to speak to approximately 80-100 warm customers per day. More than just and order taker, I would perform:

- -Assisting with additional inbound call load of up to 20 calls per day
- -Minor troubleshooting over the phone for refrigeration or post mix beverage equipment and to determine if an request onsite technician visit was required
- -Assist in resolving account issues including credit card payments from customers
- -Communicating with stakeholders and coordinating with local field sales reps to execute brand strategy and achieve monthly, quarterly and yearly sales targets
- -Building and maintaining rapport with customers over repeated contact to help build a trusting business relationship

### Education

Singleton High School (1995 - 2000)

Coder Academy

Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2020)